get up!
Brave and
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Oh, oh, oh.
Lush green forests.
As far as the eye can see.
A gentle stream.
With crystal clear water.
Flowers and plants.
Teeming with color and life.
Beautiful beaches in every region.
This is a tale of the
land of Wano when its
skies were clear and
its people flourished.
in a paradise secluded from the world.
You're saying that a
mountain was chasing you?
That's right, and the thing
was groaning at us too.
An ill omen.
Perhaps you awakened the
wrath of the mountain god.
Just kidding.
But you look quite happy after
such a frightful encounter.
What else happened?
Can't fool you, huh?
We finally caught it.
What an adorable little boar!
If we take it to the capital,
we'll get a platinum coin for him!
What?
You could buy a house
with that kind of money!
The boss of the Kurokoma
family has been looking
for a white boar to put on
display in his storefront!
He had a reward poster put
out for it and everything!
But he shouldn't put it on display.
White boars are divine
messengers, not decorations.
Hmm?
Kin'emon?
Stealing money from our
shop again, are you?
Saru, we've known each
other since childhood.
Give me a break here.
We're like family.
You can spare a little money for me.
You're just going to gamble it all away.
Do you know how much you owe me?
because I certainly do.
The next time you lay your
filthy fingers on my money,
I'll sell your organs to cover the debt.
If you can't pay me back, I'll take
your clothes as clothes later on!
It's my tattoo sale!
Oh, please don't cry like me,
although a funeral is the proper
place for that, I suppose.
Did something happen?
Not with the surface, no.
But after the cremation, when we were
about to gather up my father's bones,
he showed up!
He put a pot on top of the remains and
started cooking Odin with the fire!
It seems the young Lord Odin
has no talent for sailing.
As of today, he has attempted to
leave the country illegally 38 times.
Rather impressive that he survived.
I suspect that you know much of this,
but allow me to offer a glimpse into
some of your son's accomplishments.
Before he was even a year
old, he sent his nanny flying.
When he was two, he was swift
enough to catch two hares at once.
When he was four, he hurled a
boulder and knocked out a bear.
When he was six, he spent all his time at
the pleasure halls, wasting royal money.
When he was eight,
for some reason he
instigated a fight with a
bunch of violent patrons
at a gambling parlor.
He defeated them all, naturally.
By the time he was nine, he
was blacklisted by the Yakuza.
He repaid this slight by burning down
the gambling hall he was banned from,
instigating a gang war.
Then, at the ripe age of ten years
old, he was arrested for assault.
Sent to the quarries as punishment,
he developed an impressive talent
while serving his sentence.
That is to say, he became a
master stonemason in no time.
Thanks, of course, to his Kozuki blood.
From there, he left prison
and reformed his ways.
Then there's the tale of the drought.
When wells were drying up in the capital,
he couldn't bear the
sight of people suffering.
So when he was 14, he redirected
the river to run through the city.
This caused a massive flood, and
an arrest warrant was issued again.
This was his cue to flee,
so he traversed that river in hopes
of escaping the country by sea.
Needless to say, he failed miserably.
Then, when he was 15, he threatened a
priest to let him hide in a mountain temple.
He brought back women from
the capital every night.
Before long, he had his own harem.
This is clearly the work of a
monster and not a man. That said,
although he did acquire a great many
lovers, they were free to leave at any time.
Of course, not everyone
involved was quite so happy.
The women's boyfriends, for example,
and their parents, and their husbands.
A team of skillful samurai
even joined their cause.
The young lord welcomed their
challenge and stood his ground.
This later came to be
known as the Harem War.
The Hilgaro family
attempted to restore peace.
But when all attempts failed, they were
drawn into the chaos of battle as well.
I've heard enough.
Right.
The young lord is now 18 years old.
He continues to stir up trouble
at a healthy pace to this day.
Report over.
I need you to deliver this to Odin
without speaking on the matter.
It's like I just won the lottery.
My lucky star is shining on me today.
If I give this to old boss
Kurokoma, I'll be rich.
Hey, while we're at it, how about
you give me all your clothes?
You're not getting away this time!
Whoa, whoa, whoa, wait!
Give me a break!
I'll pay you guys back today!
I'm about to hit it big!
More excuses!
It's true!
Just let me go to the Kurokoma Mansion!
Kin'emon?
Oh, him?
That little thug who stole our money?
Well, here's an easy solution.
Catch him and fillet him alive.
But don't engage him one-on-one.
He's a punk, but he's strong.
Real strong.
I have been entrusted with 60 silver,
but simply spending it would be a waste.
Right?
I'll take this pot here.
I'm running an errand for someone.
All right, that'll be 30 silver.
Here. Thanks, kid.
Oops, I bought the wrong pot.
I needed the bigger one.
All right, but that
one is 60 silver. Easy.
I paid you 30 for the first pot, so
I'll give it back and that makes 60.
Got it.
Thanks, pal.
What the hell?
Well, he just conned that
guy out of 30 silver.
Easy money.
Psst, dingito.
Oh, Cain, you scared me.
Look, I scored me something good.
Oh, Zeus.
Our next drink will be in the afterlife.
Take it easy, friend.
Excuse me.
I'll be taking my leave.
But I'm sorry for your loss.
That was amazing. So cool.
What did he just do?
That was one of his
trademark Odin speeches.
Just to be clear, you came to arrest me.
Well, yes.
But personally, I don't want to
arrest you, so if you could bribe me,
that would help us both.
Well, this is new.
Usually it's me people are running from.
Ah, there must be a fire
or something of the sort.
Are you out of your mind?
You can't bring that thing into the city!
What?
But it's just a little boar!
Kurokoma doesn't want that for business!
He wants to use it as a decoy
to destroy the Hyogoro family!
What does that mean?
I mean that thing's
parent will come for it!
We'll have a giant boar charging
through town in his nevel now!
Up I go!
What do you mean, it's parrot?
According to ancient documents, it's
white and strong and big as a mountain.
Why do you think everyone
calls it the mountain god?
What?
They say that several hundred years ago,
it destroyed an entire
village in one night.
That sounded crazy, so I
figured it was just a legend.
But now, there's a white boar
here right in front of our eyes.
So that must mean the
mountain god is real,
it's come to swallow us alive!
It's already upon us.
Run for it!
It's all our fault—the capital's
doomed—and it's my fault.
my fault
Oh,
my God.
Kozuki Oden!
Pardon me, I couldn't help but
overhear what you just said.
I don't need to know how
you came upon that boar.
But why don't you hand it over to me?
And I'll settle this.
Well, thanks a lot, you little pork chop.
Now we're all gonna die.
Stop squealing.
I told you, just give that thing to me.
Now, hold on a sec.
You can't take this from me.
I'm gonna sell it and get rich.
So hands off, I've got a mountain of
debts I need to pay off right away.
Then I'm gonna use the rest on
investments to get even more rich.
That's really him?
Kotakiyotin?
Adults are nothing but a bunch of clowns.
But this man, this man alone, I respect.
Its child is here.
That's the only reason
why the mountain god
would come to a place where humans dwell.
You mean, some idiot stole
its child and brought it here?
We must placate the
mountain god and quickly.
There should be a white
piglet somewhere close by.
If we can't send it back to the mountain
where it belongs, the capital will drop us.
Help, I'm stuck! Somebody!
This moving house is people and all!
Daddy, no!
It's a nightmare!
So there you are, finally found you!
This is all your fault, you boar thief!
Who's the boar thief, you boar thief?
Send that thing back to the
mountain before we're dead!
You know what'll happen when
the big one gets a whiff of it?
We're done for!
It'll eat us! What?
We had no idea this was gonna
happen when we took that piglet!
My two buddies got eaten up
by the mountain god already!
The clothes smelled
like his baby, you see?
And then it swallowed
your friend Otsuru, too!
Wait, Otsuru was there?
We needed a plan to get that
white boar back from you!
So we took Otsuru as a hostage,
but then on the way to the city,
it came out of nowhere and ate them.
They're dead and it's all your fault!
Hey, wait!
You know what'll happen when
the big one gets a whiff of it?
We're done, boy! It's Alina!
Out of my way!
Here it comes!
What?
King stole something again?
I'm so sorry.
Please let me pay for it.
Keen, it's time you get a real job.
You can't keep angering
the Yakuza like this.
They're going to kill you.
So what?
Not like anyone's going to care if I die.
Did you just hit me with a rock?
Give her back right there!
Oh, my God.
Stop it, you fool!
If you haunt the mountain god, then
the land of water will pay the price!
I'll cut you open, tear through your
belly, and I'll take Tsuru back!
I don't care if you're a guy!
Oh, no!
Come on, team!
Get out of there!
I must admit, that fellow has guts.
If Saru dies because of me...
...then I want to die, too.
Hey! Four!
This is what you're looking for!
So it was you!
I should have known!
Kozuki Oden, the prodigal
son, at it again!
You'll make a fine hot pot!
This is the last straw!
How could you do this?
My mother was easily!
Take that!
No, you don't understand.
My daughter is dead!
I brought that boy here.
It's my fault that the capital is ruined.
Your loved ones are dead because of me.
Oden, two-sword style!
No!
No! No!
He's really something.
Let's pack it up.
They say that the people and houses
swallowed that day were so great
in number that they could have formed
a new town in the boar's stomach.
A quarter of the capital was destroyed,
but miraculously, not a single
one of its citizens died.
That was horrible!
Odin was amazing.
I almost cheered for him back there.
I wish I could say thank you, but I can't.
You saved us, but you're the
one who started this mess.
Everyone, please listen.
It wasn't Odin's fault, it was...
Don't do anything unnecessary.
Poor Odin, sir!
I'm sorry to give this to you
at a time of such revelry.
Disavowed, am I?
And expelled from the capital, too?
Laughable shogun.
Truly pathetic.
So much power, and I'm
still too much for you.
The capital cannot contain my greatness.
Finally, I'll leave at once.
Wherever the sun falls
is where I shall sleep.
But now, I'm hungry.
The mountain god incident
marked a new beginning for Odin.
Who was still quite young at the time?
What's the matter?
Don't cry I'm not crying at all.
Listen, I would die for that man, Otsuru.
Um, okay.
Well said, I would die for Lord Odin
too. Hey! Digital! Wait! What? What?
Kozuki Odin! Kozuki Odin!
Kozuki Odin!
That man is one of a kind! Indeed!
And I'll follow him for
the rest of my life!
I was his fan first!
Yeah, well, I'm his biggest fan!
And his first follower!
I wish I was free like them!
All the men who watched these events
transpire took a hesitant step forward,
wishing that they could
go along with Odin.
And thus the capital
tilted, ever so slightly.
What an honor to see you, Lord Odin.
Please come right in.
Lord Yasui's been looking
forward to your arrival.
Don't lie, I know he hasn't.
That's right, you idiot.
Who would look forward
to a visit from you?
What is this, your entourage?
What do you miscreants want?
Hey, uncle!
Oh, don't speak to me like that.
Oh, wait!
There's a puddle of mud!
Please proceed.
Better to walk across my back.
Don't sully yourself.
Who is this guy?
He creeps me out!
He's my new manservant, and you'd
best leave him alone. Ah, yes.
Lord Yasui was very kind to take me in.
Pleasure to meet you.
I'm Kurozumi Oruji.